Friends, in today's video I will tell you all
how you can open the monthly statement of
ICICI Bank that comes on your mobile phone.
Now I saw that
before this we had made a video in which
many such comments came that it is
not opening, so
I have come with the solution of that problem
and how will you be able to open it, 100%
you will be able to open it after watching this video,
let me show you here by giving live proof, I am here, I am
here,
okay, before that let me show you here,
as if you click on the statement,
you will get to see the complete file, so
whatever is your name, like your
name is Pawan, okay
Pawan, in Pawan you have to write small P,
when you enter the password, write small P, P
AV N, you have to write your name like this, you have to
write only four words, you do not have to
write much, like your name is Dheeraj, so D
small W  You have to write D, you have to
write DHIR like this, then you have to
write four words of your name in small, okay,
after that if your date of birth is like 12
05 2019, whatever it is, then what you have to do
and when you write the name, you have to write your name in
small, ABC, as I am telling you, by doing
ABC, okay, you have to
write it in small like this, after that 12
05, something like this, only when you write it,
your name will open, the password will open, this is the
password of the name, which should be four words
short, and the date of birth is
1205, so 1205 has to be written like this, okay,
after that what you have to do here is that first you have to
download this PDF,
come from here and click here and
download it, I will download it, it is
downloaded here, it is
not opening from here, if you are entering the password and it is
wrong, then what you have to do
after downloading, you have to go to the
file manager in your mobile,
you have to click on the file manager here,
like you can click here  If you click, the
statement that you have just downloaded will appear in
front of you here, you can see it. So
what you have to do is
click on this statement. Now what you have to do is
you have to enter your password here, as I have
put it here and shown it,
because a lot of comments had come that it was
not opening, for this I
tried again, you can see here that it has
opened in front of you. Now what should you do?
Still, if yours is not opening, then
what should you do in that condition? What
happens? In our mobile, there is an app to open two-three
PDFs. So,
you have only one PDF which is
PDF viewer, it will open in that only, which is the red
PDF viewer, in the other app, it does
not open.
Even if you enter the correct password,
what will you have to do for that, that is, how to push it and
keep it. You can see here that it has been
selected. After it is selected,
what do you have to do, you have to come
here, come to the peacock option below,
after that it is given here, when you  If you
get the option of more then it will be given that it will open in
other app, so what you have to do is you have to
click on this, click on other app,
what happens after clicking here is that our app automatically
opens in this or it does
not open even if we enter the correct password, so what you have to do is
click on PDF view,
I have clicked on PDF view, you
can see that it is showing slightly blue, I will make it always,
after that
when the interface will come like this, then you have to
write the four words which is the small letter of your name, after that write the date, write the
date and month and click on open,
your PDF will open,
if you liked the video and your problem has been solved then
like the video and
subscribe to the channel,
thank you